(Sheldon:)...but this has truly been
a transformative evening.
(Amy:)I'm a little surprised to hear you
feeling so positive.
(Sheldon:)Well, you're an excellent neuroscientist,
you're a wonderful girlfriend...
(Sheldon:)...and...
- And?
- Doesn't matter, does it?
(Amy:)I'm proud of you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)And a complete sucker.
(1.(Redraws tic-tac-toe board)Sheldon:)Oh, yeah.
(3.(Winds up jack-in-the-box until it pops out.)Sheldon:)There he is.
(4. Sheldon(singing):)And the home of the brave
(5.(Knocks over first of intricate domino pattern)Sheldon:)Don't stop. Yes, keep going.
(5.(Knocks over first of intricate domino pattern)Sheldon:)Just like that.
Almost there. Almost there.